<resources xmlns:tools="http://schemas.android.com/tools">
    <string name="app_name">Mathub</string>
    <string name="first">If the unknown of the equation is under the sign of the square root,then such an equation is called irrational.</string>
    <string name="second"> Many situations in life are described by irrational equations.</string>
    <string name="third"> First irrational equation`</string>
    <string name="fourth"> Second irrational equation`</string>
    <string name="fifth">The absolute value or modulus of a non-negative number ğ‘¥ is called the number ğ‘¥ itself:  The modulus of a negative number ğ‘¥ is called its opposite: </string>
    <string name="sixth">|ğ‘¥| = ğ‘¥</string>
    <string name="seventh">The modulus of a negative number ğ‘¥ is called its opposite: |ğ‘¥| = âˆ’ğ‘¥.</string>
    <string name="eight">1.|a| = 0</string>
    <string name="ninth">2.|a * b| = |a| * |b|</string>
    <string name="ten">3.|a/b| = |a| / |b|</string>
    <string name="str11">4.|a|Â² = aÂ²</string>
    <string name="str12">5.|-a| = |a|</string>
    <string name="str13">Consider the equation âˆ£ğ‘¥âˆ£=ğ´, where ğ´ is a real number. It follows from the definition and properties of the module that the equation âˆ£ğ‘¥âˆ£=ğ´:</string>
    <string name="str14">2) in the case of ğ´=0, it has the only solution: ğ‘¥=0 </string>
    <string name="str15">3) For ğ´>0, it has two solutions: ğ‘¥ = ğ´ and ğ‘¥ = âˆ’ğ´</string>
    <string name="str16">We have already considered the designation of some sets on the number line: (âˆ’âˆ;âˆ),(ğ‘;+âˆ),[ğ‘;+âˆ),(âˆ’âˆ;ğ‘],(âˆ’âˆ;ğ‘)</string>
    <string name="str17">If a number ğ‘¥ simultaneously satisfies the inequalities ğ‘¥ more than âˆ’4 and ğ‘¥ less than 5, then it satisfies the two-sided inequality  ğ‘¥ greater than -4 but less than 5.</string>
    <string name="str18">The set of all numbers satisfying the two-sided inequality ğ‘¥ more than -4 and less than 5 is called a numerical interval and is denoted as (âˆ’4;5).</string>
    <string name="str19">Arithmetic progression is the numerical sequence in which each term, starting from the second, is equal to its predecessor plus the same number.</string>
    <string name="str20">If {ğ‘ğ‘›} is an arithmetic progression, then for any natural number ğ‘› the following formula is true: ğ‘ğ‘›+1=ğ‘ğ‘›+ğ‘‘
The number ğ‘‘ is called the difference of the arithmetic progression.</string>
    <string name="str21">The ğ‘›-th term of the progression with the first term ğ‘1 and the difference ğ‘‘ is expressed by the following formula: ğ‘ğ‘›=ğ‘1+ğ‘‘(ğ‘›âˆ’1). This formula is called the formula for the ğ‘›-th term of an arithmetic progression.</string>
    <string name="str22">Given the first term of the arithmetic progression {ğ‘ğ‘›} and the difference ğ‘1=0 and ğ‘‘=2. he first five members of the progression?</string>
    <string name="str23">The percentage of a number can be found in different ways.</string>
    <string name="str24">For example:</string>
    <string name="str25">Let is find 18% of the number 300.</string>
    <string name="str26">I variant. Let is take action.</string>
    <string name="str27">First, find 1% of 300.
        300:100=3</string>
    <string name="str28">Multiply the obtained number by the number of percentages.</string>
    <string name="str29">3Â·18=54%</string>
    <string name="str30">So 18% of 300 is equal to 54%.</string>
    <string name="str31">II variant. Let is present the percentage in the form of a regular fraction.</string>
    <string name="str32">If you want to find the percent of a number, you need to:</string>
    <string name="str33">1) write the percentage in the form of a regular fraction.</string>
    <string name="str34">2) multiply the given number by the received fraction.</string>


</resources>